{
    "id": "a563b494c8f441798e1f941fe0d47160",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you are really interested in her, why don't you ask her ...................... to a movie?",
            "description": "\r\nTo ask somebody out is to invite them on a date.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked ........................... but nobody had seen my cat.",
            "description": "To ask around is to ask the same question to many people.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "over",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Your bill adds ........................ to 300 dollars.",
            "description": "Add up to can mean be equal.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't get out unless you back ........................ your car.",
            "description": "To back up a car is to reverse it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody backed me ................................. when I announced my decision to quit my job.",
            "description": "To back somebody up is to support them.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The car blew ........................ after it collided with the truck.",
            "description": "To blow up is to explode.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "over",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Ask the children to blow ....................... the balloons for the party.",
            "description": "To blow up balloons is to inflate them.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The fire fighters had to break ………………….. the building to save the trapped women and children.",
            "description": "To break into a building is to enter forcibly.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car broke ........................ in the thunder storm.",
            "description": "When a machine or a vehicle breaks down, it stops working.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman broke .......................... when the police told her that they had strong evidences against her.",
            "description": "To break down is to get upset and cry.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If the task seems unmanageable break it ......................... into smaller parts.",
            "description": "To break it down is to divide it into smaller parts.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The thieves broke ...................... at night and stole diamonds and jewels.",
            "description": "To break in is to force entry to a building.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}